<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economy on Home | Jie An</title>
    <link>https://leslieaj.gitee.io/tags/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economy on Home | Jie An</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leslieaj.gitee.io/tags/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Secrets To ML – Even In This Down Economy</title>
      <link>https://leslieaj.gitee.io/blog/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslieaj.gitee.io/blog/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Nulla fermentum blandit metus sit amet congue. Nunc hendrerit eleifend magna, quis posuere nulla eleifend eget. Pellentesque quis nulla eu massa facilisis sodales in quis urna. Vestibulum aliquam metus id risus volutpat iaculis. Sed malesuada nunc cursus risus consectetur suscipit. Quisque sit amet leo mattis, sagittis purus eu, tristique sapien. Vestibulum gravida dictum aliquam. Etiam magna neque, tempus et aliquet sed, sollicitudin sed tellus. Sed euismod, lorem eget aliquet ultrices, nisl eros hendrerit nunc, in gravida augue leo id diam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Active learning of One-Clock Timed Automata using Constraint Solving</title>
      <link>https://leslieaj.gitee.io/fullpublications/atva2022a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leslieaj.gitee.io/fullpublications/atva2022a/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Active automata learning in the framework of Angluin&amp;rsquo;s $ L^* $ algorithm has been applied to learning many kinds of automata models. In applications to timed models such as timed automata, the main challenge is to determine guards on the clock value in transitions as well as which transitions reset the clock. In this paper, we introduce a new algorithm for active learning of deterministic one-clock timed automata and timed Mealy machines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
